ILR School "ILR Newsletter" and Other Student Publications /3074 PUBS
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School "ILR Newsletter" and Other Student Publications
1945-1961
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (NYSSILR)
/3074 PUBS
0.5 cubic feet
0.5 linear ft.
Publications (documents).
ILR School student newsletters and other publications
8436892
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, October 15, 2013
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, February 22, 2019
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of issues of student publications ILR News, ILR Newsletter, ILR Commentator, and related materials.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations
8436892
- Introduction to Industrial and Labor Relations, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Includes syllabus; Spring 1946.
- ILR News, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- ILR News, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- ILR News, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- ILR News, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- ILR Newsletter, 1950-1954 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Also includes undated issues.
- ILR Newsletter, 1956-1959 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- ILR Newsletter, 1960-1961 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- ILR Commentator, 1948-1949 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- ILR Commentator, 1946-1949 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- ILR News, 1946-1948 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  Gift of Harriet Morel Oxman
- Miscellany (Box 1, Folder 12)
  Includes constitution and by-laws of the student's organization of the School of Industrial and Labor Relations